Money, Money, Money
I work all night
I work all day to pay the bills
I have to pay ain't it sad
And still there never seems to be a single penny left for me that's too bad
In my dreams
I have a plan
If I got me a wealthy man
I wouldn't have to work at all
I'd fool around and have a ball
Money, money, money must be funny in the rich man's world
Money, money, money always sunny in the rich man's world
Ah ah ah ah ah ah
All the things
I could do if
I had a little money it's a rich man's world
It's a rich man's world
A man like that is hard to find but
I can't get him off my mind ain't it sad
And if he happens to be free
I bet he wouldn't fancy me that's too bad
So I must leave
I'll have to go to
Las Vegas or
Monaco And win a fortune in a game my life will never be the same
Money, money, money must be funny in the rich man's world
Money, money, money always sunny in the rich man's world
Ah ah ah ah ah ah
All the things
I could do if
I had a little money it's a rich man's world
Money, money, money must be funny in the rich man's world
Money, money, money always sunny in the rich man's world
Ah ah ah ah ah ah
All the things
I could do if
I had a little money
It's a rich man's world